[music]
>> In the previous release, we added
capability to synchronize prices for
catalogs which are associated with
markets. Yes, markets which are
representing different regions, and you
might want to actually define different
tax and price and localization rules per
market. So, price is very important. And
one more, it's all for often very
important to allow user
or buyer in the local market to buy in
local currency.
So, I have couple of orders here where
customer
the same customer
get the same item
but delivered to the different different
locations. So, in one case it was US
dollars
and in other case we are in Denmark uh
this customer paid in Danish crowns
because the items will be delivered into
Denmark. So, we the the currency
demonstrated or presented to customer is
the presentment currency.
Currency used at the checkout time.
In the Business Central, we used to
import both of them but create sales
documents only in the store currency,
the default currency
configured in the Shopify admin
not anymore.
Switching to Business Central
and opening Shopify shop card and scroll
a little bit down
a little bit more, order processing. If
you do not see the field, try to click
show more. The currency handling, the
new field. It has two options, shop
currency, the default one, to make sure
that there are no sudden changes. As
soon as you upgrade, it will continue to
create orders the same way it used to do
that.
But you can always switch to presentment
currency.
And actually you can do that at any
point of time.
Then, let's navigate to orders
and synchronize orders from Shopify.
All right, we received three orders. Two
of them we already explored.
And let's create sales document for
them.
All right, what do we see here?
We see the
store currency and the presentment
currency, which are blank, means local
currency. So, these ones are used in the
local currency. But the next one, the
next order
let's navigate to it
and create sales document.
You can see that
amounts are different. This is what we
uh amount in the in the store currency,
and this is presentment currency.
Because we configured
uh orders to be created in presentment
currency
you can see the new field here,
processed currency, which is populated
as soon as you process document. So, now
the
created document
is created in the in the
presentment currency, in Danish crowns.
So, if I will navigate to my sales order
you can see Danish crowns all all over
the place, including the currency code.
All right.
What if
I want to change something? I cannot
change this presentment currency, it's
not editable, but I can always
unlink processed document
correct?
Open
the store
switch to shop currency
for example, or vice versa
return back to the order
and create sales document again.
So, now when system was
connector creates new sales document it
use setting from the Shopify shop card.
So, now we have the second one
and you can see that amounts are in the
store currency or local currency in my
case, 450 in both in both scenarios. So,
as you can see, it's very easy to
uh manipulate the data and experiment
which works for you and try if you want
to
activate the new capability or not. You
can always
reactivate
switch it back and recreate orders if
necessary.
So, you can see that
creation orders in the presentment
currency it's a safe and a logical
step after defining currencies in the
catalogs linked to the markets.
So, two features work seamlessly
together and uh
you are very welcome to try and provide
a feedback to us using one of the
channels like Viva Engage or LinkedIn.
You can find more videos on our YouTube
channel.
Thank you.